Walter B. Wriston Papers MS134
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiovisual Media, 1950 -- 2008; 1982 -- 2004; MS134.004; 1.5 Linear Feet
  - Doing Business In the Information Age, DMA [Direct Marketing Association] Annual Financial Service Conference, 1989-06-08; MS134.004.030.00005 (Case 30)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 REEL #2 AUDIO CD. The CD is a Verbatim DataLifePlus CD-R. The file type is Winamp media. The paper copy of the speech is in Series 1, box 10, and item #00011.
  - Walter B. Wriston, the Derek McGinty Show, 1992-09-25; MS134.004.030.00006 (Case 30)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5386 #001. The CD is a Fujifilm CD-R. The file type is Winamp media. Also written on the CD is WAMU 88.5 FM The American University. Walter Wriston discusses his book Twilight of Sovereignty.
  - Walter B. Wriston - Twilight of Sovereignty, The Commonwealth Club, 1992-11-10; MS134.004.030.00007 (Case 30)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 REEL #3 AUDIO CD. The CD is a Verbatim DataLifePlus CD-R. The file type is Winamp media. This is a recording of Walter Wriston's speech at the Commonwealth Club of California. The paper copy of the speech is in Series 1, box 10, and item #00010. The speech was also published in The Commonwealth: The Weekly Publication of the Commonwealth Club of California, there is a copy in Series 3, box 27, and item #00024.
  - CD_ROM_WBW_Computer Files - Professional Files from New York City and Connecticut Computers, 2006-12-10; MS134.004.030.00008 (Case 30)
    This CD-ROM contains the files extracted from Walter Wriston's computers in New York City and Connecticut. The CD is a FujiFilm CD-R. Also on the CD is written Files in both IBM and Mac formats including Bits, Bytes & Balance Sheets 12-10-06 KLW. KLW are the initials of Kurt Willett who organized Mr. Wriston's files for transfer to the Digital Collections and Archives. The CD-ROM contains five folders Book-Twilight, BB&BS Files, CTMacProfessional, PCProfessional, and WBW Appelworks. There are also files produced for the transfer of Mr. Wriston's files to the Digital Collections and Archives FletcherAudio&VideoTapes (Microsoft Word Document), MacProfessionalDocuments (Microsoft Excel Worksheet), WBWBio (Microsoft Word Document), WBWTimeline (Microsoft Word Document), and WBWWebsite (Microsoft Word Document). In the folder Book-Twilight, there are six additional folders Book3Aug91, Book 3_9_91, Book as of 6_28_90, Book as of 9_16_91, Book on 18 July 91, and Untitled Chapter 2feb 1991. The file types in folder Book-Twilight and its subfolders were too old to open, so they were resaved into plain text documents and the originals were kept the same. In the folder BB&BS Files, there are sixteen Microsoft Word Documents as well as two additional folders McCartyDisk and McCartyNew which also contain Microsoft Word Documents. In the folder CTMacProfessional, there are fifty-four Microsoft Word Documents and one Microsoft Excel Worksheet. In the folder titled PCProfessional, there are twenty-eight Microsoft Word Documents, one Microsoft Excel Worksheet, and one Adobe Acrobat 7.0 Document. In the folder WBW Appleworks, the files were Mac formatted but could not be opened even on a MAC, so the files were resaved into plain text documents.
  - A Network for the World, Reuters, 1984-02-10; MS134.004.030.00009 (Case 30)
    This DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #7. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD ends at Chapter 6 and it does not contain footage of Walter Wriston, but it does have some footage of Citicorp.
  - Greetings to Walt, Citibank, 1984-07-13; MS134.004.030.00010 (Case 30)
    This DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #003. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R for General. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD was made for Walter Wriston's retirement.
  - Airport Capabilities: Managing Construction and Public Convenience, 1985; MS134.004.030.00011 (Case 30)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #8. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD discusses the projects undertaken by Bechtel. Walter Wriston was a director of Bechtel Investments, Inc.
  - The New Enlightenment: The Death of Socialism (DVD 1 of 2), 1986; MS134.004.030.00012 (Case 30)
    This DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD does not contain footage of Walter Wriston.
  - The New Enlightenment: The Death of Socialism (DVD 2 of 2), 1986; MS134.004.031.00001 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD does not contain footage of Walter Wriston.
  - Krulwich and Wriston Pieces, CBS Morning News, 1986; MS134.004.031.00002 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #006. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There are two segments from CBS Morning News' Economics Correspondent, Robert Krulwich. One segment is on the effects of car companies offering loans and the other segment is on the Big Bang in London.
  - Hi-Tech Capitalism, Opinions, UK Channel 4 Television, 1986-07-24; MS134.004.031.00003 (Case 31)
    A transcript of Mr. Wriston's remarks is in Series 3, box 25, and item #00028. The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #002. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time.
  - Walter B. Wriston, Strictly Business, 1986-10; MS134.004.031.00004 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #001. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R for General. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD contains the entire episode of "Strictly Business" with Jack Cafferty as the anchor. The DVD includes commercials as well as some of the next television program.
  - A Message from John S. Reed, 1987-05-20; MS134.004.031.00005 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD is a report from John S. Reed, Chairman of Citicorp, about the decisions made by the Citicorp Board.
  - How Communications Technology is Changing Our World, The Open Mind, 1992-09-16; MS134.004.031.00006 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #010. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file is Nero Show Time. Walter Wriston is a guest on the show to discuss his book, Twilight of Sovereignty.
  - Walter B. Wriston Comments, Wall Street Week with Louis Rukeyser, 1992-09-25; MS134.004.031.00007 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #005. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R for General. The file type is Nero Show Time. Walter Wriston was a guest on the show to discuss his book Twilight of Sovereignty.
  - Is the Information Revolution the Greatest Revolution Since the Industrial Revolution?, The Telecommunications & Information Revolution, 1995 -- 1996; MS134.004.031.00008 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #6. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. Walter Wriston and James P. Hoge are both guests on the show, The Telecommunications & Information Revolution.
  - Hamilton College Commencement (DVD 1 of 2), 1996-05-19; MS134.004.031.00009 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #9. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. Walter Wriston receives an Honorary LL.D. during the commencement ceremony. Mr. Wriston is awarded the degree in DVD 1 Chapter 18 at 53:19.
  - Hamilton College Commencement - Final Minutes (DVD 2 of 2), 1996-05-19; MS134.004.031.00010 (Case 31)
  - Money: Back to the Future?, Claremont McKenna College, 1996-11-20; MS134.004.031.00011 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #10. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. A copy of Wriston's speech is located in Series 1, box 13, and item #00003.
  - Shearman & Sterling and Citibank Yesterday and Tomorrow, Boca Raton Resort and Club, 1998-04-24; MS134.004.031.00012 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #007. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. A copy of Mr. Wriston's speech is located in Series 1 box 13, and item #00008
  - Electric Money, PBS, 2001; MS134.004.031.00013 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number DVD VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #5. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time.
  - Meet the Press, 2002-08-11; MS134.004.031.00014 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The transcript of the Mr. Wriston's appearance is in Series 3, box 25, and item #00032.
  - Fletcher in the Information Age, Convocation Speech Delivered at Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University, 2003-09-03; MS134.004.031.00015 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #004. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. A copy of Mr. Wriston's speech is located in Series 1, box 15, and item #00001. Walter Wriston was unable to attend the convocation ceremony, but his speech was read by Academic Dean Lisa Lynch. At convocation, Walter Wriston was also awarded the Class of 1947 Distinguished Leadership Award.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Bob Chitester, The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00016 (Case 31)
    The DVD is copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #018. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00038.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Charles Brunie, The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00017 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #014. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00038.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Herbert Pardes, The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00018 (Case 31)
    The DVD is copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #017. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00038.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Hugh Carey, The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00019 (Case 31)
    The DVD is copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #016. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00037-00038.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Peter W. Huber (DVD 1 of 2), The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00020 (Case 31)
    The DVD is copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #013. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00038.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Peter W. Huber (Part 2), The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00021 (Case 31)
    The DVD is copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #012. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00038.
  - A Conversation with Walter Wriston and Robert D. McTeer Jr., The Idea Channel, 2004; MS134.004.031.00022 (Case 31)
    The DVD is copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #015. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is some additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00038.
  - Interview, Lou Dobbs Tonight, 2004-04; MS134.004.031.00023 (Case 31)
    There is additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 25, and item #00035.
  - Interview, Bloomberg Television, 2004-04-02; MS134.004.031.00024 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5199 REEL #11. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is additional information about the interview in Series 3, box 31, and item #00034.
  - Citigroup Honors Walter B. Wriston for receiving The Presidential Medal of Freedom Award, The Links Club, New York City, 2004-06-21; MS134.004.031.00025 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. There is additional information in Series 5, box 033, and item #00008-00010. The DVD contains footage of the reception at the Links Club where Mr. Wriston is given a piece of umbrella art. The video "The Eminently Quotable Walter Wriston" was also shown.
  - The Eminently Quotable Walter B. Wriston, Citigroup, 2004-06-21; MS134.004.031.00026 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD was created by Citigroup to commemorate Walter Wriston receiving the Presidential Medal of Freedom Award.
  - President G.W. Bush presents The Presidential Medal of Freedom Awards, C-SPAN2, 2004-06-23; MS134.004.031.00027 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is not labeled with the job number. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD consists of the Presidential Medal of Freedom Award Ceremony. Walter Wriston was unable to attend, but his brother-in-law, Robert Dineen, and his daughter, Catherine B. Quintal, accepted the award on his behalf.
  - Wriston, 2004-07-15; MS134.004.031.00028 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #011. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD consists of The Eminently Quotable Walter Wriston, footage of the Citigroup reception for Walter Wriston commemorating his Presidential Medal of Freedom Award, and C-SPAN2 footage of the Presidential Medal of Freedom Award Ceremony.
  - Walter Wriston Memorial, Christ Church, 2005-02-24; MS134.004.031.00029 (Case 31)
    The DVD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The DVD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5385 REEL #008. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X. The file type is Nero Show Time. The DVD is Mr. Wriston's memorial service at Christ Church.
  - Electronic Money, 1982; MS134.004.045.00001 (Box 45)
    This videocassette was created by Citibank Television Center, One Court Square, Long Island City, NY 11120, 718-248-3897. Running time of the film is 7:45 minutes.
    videocassette
  - The Story of Money: All About Money, 1999; MS134.004.045.00002 (Box 45)
    This videocassette is a documentary created by A&E Television Networks in 1999. They are the copyright holders for this film. Running time is approximately 100 minutes.
  - [Unititled], 1950 -- 1990; MS134.004.045.00003 (Box 45)
    The audio tape is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5386 REEL #001. There is no other identifying information on the tape. However, VIDIPAX job and reel numbers for this tape are identical to the numbers on items MS134.004.030.00002 and MS134.004.030.00006. These CDs contain audio recordings of Walter Wriston's appearances on Face the Nation in 1982 and the Derek McGinty Show in 1992, respectively.
    audiocassette
  - Senior Management Meeting, 1978-01-18; MS134.004.045.00004 (Box 45)
    The DVD was made by Corporate Media Solutions (Citigroup Corporate Affairs) in 2008. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X.
    DVD
  - The New Enlightenment, part 1 [DVD 1 of 2], 1986; MS134.004.045.00005 (Box 45)
    The DVD was made by Citigroup Media Services. The DVD is a Verbatim DVD-R 8X.
  - The New Enlightenment, part 2 and Atlas - 14 minutes [DVD 2 of 2], 1986; MS134.004.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - The Story of Citigroup. 100 Countries. 200 Years., 2007; MS134.004.045.00007 (Box 45)
    The DVD was made by Citigroup in 2007.
  - The Legacy of Walter Wriston hosted by the Manhattan Institute, 2008-06-19; MS134.004.045.00008 (Box 45)
    The DVD is by Citigroup and is a DVD-R Verbatim.
  - Kuala Lumpur conference, (to Bank), 1966; MS134.004.045.00009 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 REEL #4. The recording is a speech given by Walter Wriston.
    compact disk
  - Citibusiness to Citibank microcassette, 1971 -- 1982; MS134.004.045.00010 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 REEL #6. The recording is a speech given by Walter Wriston.
  - WBW - Twilight of Sovereignty to Fletcher, 1992-11-10; MS134.004.045.00011 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 REEL #3. The recording is a speech given by Walter Wriston to the Fletcher School at Tufts University, regarding his book, the Twilight of Sovereignty.
  - Draft of Speech (to Fletcher), 1990 -- 2005; MS134.004.045.00012 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by VIDIPAX. The CD is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 REEL #9. The recording is of Walter Wriston rehersing a speech that he would give to the Fletcher School at Tufts University. It may be the speech Fletcher in the Information Age, which he gave at the Fletcher convocation in 2003.
  - Planned Television Arts 'Bits, Bytes & Balance Sheets' Guests: General Alexander Haig, 10am Eastern, 2007-05-22; MS134.004.045.00013 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by Multi-Point Communications. The CD is a Memorex. The CD contains various radio interviews with General Alexander Haig discussing Walter Wriston's posthumous book, Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets. Planned Television Arts is a book publicity company.
  - Planned Television Arts 'Walter B. Wriston Bits, Bytes & Balance Sheets' Guest: George P. Shultz, 10:55am Eastern, 2008-03-13; MS134.004.045.00014 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by Multi-Point Communications. The CD is a Memorex. The CD contains various radio interviews with George P. Shultz discussing Walter Wriston's posthumous book, Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets. Planned Television Arts is a book publicity company.
  - Planned Television Arts 'Walter B. Wriston Bits, Bytes & Balance Sheets' Guest: Dean Stephen Bosworth, 8:10am Eastern, 2008-05-19; MS134.004.045.00015 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by Multi-Point Communications. The CD is a Memorex. The CD contains various radio interviews with Dean Stephen Bosworth discussing Walter Wriston's posthumous book, Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets. Planned Television Arts is a book publicity company.
  - Planned Television Arts 'Walter B. Wriston Bits, Bytes & Balance Sheets' Guest: Phil Zweig, 6:55am Eastern, 2008-07-15; MS134.004.045.00016 (Box 45)
    This audio CD is a copy made by Multi-Point Communications. The CD is a Memorex. The CD contains various radio interviews with Phil Zweig discussing Walter Wriston's posthumous book, Bits, Bytes, and Balance Sheets. Planned Television Arts is a book publicity company.
  - Citi Business, 1971 -- 1982; MS134.004.045.00017 (Box 45)
    This microcassette was made in Austria by Norelco. It is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 RL#006. This microcassette may be the original item used to make the VIDIPAX copy of 'Citibusiness to Citibank' (MS134.004.04500010).
  - Twilight Speech, MS134.004.045.00018 (Box 45)
    This microcassette was made in Austria by Norelco. It is labeled with the job number VIDIPAX JOB #5200 RL#009. This microcassette may be the original item used to make the VIDIPAX copy of '[Draft of The World Corporation-New Weight in an Old Balance]' (MS134.004.030.00001) or 'Draft of Speech (to Fletcher)' (MS134.004.045.00012).
- Subject Files, 1918 -- 2005; 1973 -- 2004; MS134.005; 3.45 Linear Feet
  This series consists of subject files relating to variety of people, organizations, events, and topics. Citibank/ Citigroup materials include press releases, correspondence and annual reports. Records relating to Municipal Union/Financial Leaders Group (MUFLG) include meeting minutes and articles from the New York Times and the Wall Street Journal. The group was established to assist in the resolution of the New York City fiscal crisis of 1975. Presidential Medal of Freedom Award materials include White House and Citigroup press releases; reception materials; and congratulatory correspondence, emails, and phone calls. Obituaries, tributes, memorial plans, and condolence letters for Walter B. Wriston are contained in this series. There is a significant amount of material relating to Walter Wriston's father, Henry Merritt Wriston, including book reviews, memorial tributes, correspondence, and press releases. Wriston's files of quotations, which he called "inspiration files" and used in his writings and speeches, are also included. Unidentified writings by Wriston, primarily printed out from his computer files, have been included here if they could not be assigned to a specific series.
  This series also includes extensive correspondence. Single letters are filed individually and correspondence is subdivided by topic, organization or person. Correspondents include Alan Greenspan, George P. Shultz, Richard Vigilante, Rose and Milton Friedman, as well as Presidential holiday cards from Ronald and Nancy Reagan. Organization-related correspondence includes American Academy of Arts & Sciences, the Business Council, the Cato Institute, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, and the White House. Topical correspondence includes condolences, political correspondence, and retirement.
  Materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by subject, except correspondence, which is subdivided by topic, then alphabetically, with material donated in 2009 is arranged in a second alphabetical run at the end of the series.
  - Alan Greenspan Correspondence, 2001; MS134.005.029.00023 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences Membership Correspondence, 2001; MS134.005.029.00024 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - Appleton High School Hall of Fame Award, 2003 -- 2004; MS134.005.029.00025 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - Artist in Residence Program Honorary Committee at Brown University, 1987; MS134.005.029.00026 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - The Business Council Correspondence, 2002; MS134.005.029.00027 (Box MS134 Shared 3)
  - Cato Institute Advisory Board Center for Trade Policy Studies Correspondence, 1999; MS134.005.029.00028 (Box MS134 Shared 3)